<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
  <title>chostett.com</title>
  <description>This is my personal home on the web. I write about games, design, technology and being human.</description>
  <link>https://www.chostett.com</link>
  <lastBuildDate>
    Tue, 12 Sep 2023 06:43:42 +0000
  </lastBuildDate>
  <ttl>20000</ttl>

    <item>
        <title>Updates to the Interface Drama Master List</title>
        <description>
             Added ESC, Human Errors, Neurocracy, A Normal Lost Phone, VIDEOVERSE and Blooming Panic to the Interface Drama Master List. Check out the new updates!
        </description>
        <link>https://chostett.com/blog/posts/2023-08-15-Interface-Drama-Master-List</link>
        <pubDate>
            Tue, 12 Sep 2023 06:43:42 +0000
        </pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
        <title>The Interface Drama Master List FAQ</title>
        <description>
             Interface dramas, also known as interface fictions or interactive narratives, are a small but growing form of game where a user interface is used to tell an immersive story. Check out definitions at the FAQ here!
        </description>
        <link>https://chostett.com/blog/posts/2023-08-15-Interface-Drama-Master-List</link>
        <pubDate>
            Wed, 23 Aug 2023 03:57:25 +0000
        </pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
        <title>The Interface Drama Master List</title>
        <description>
             Interface dramas are games that tell an immersive story through software and app interfaces. They are commonly called "desktop simulators" or "UI games" but I've found these labels to be either too prescriptive or too general to describe this emergent genre. And so, I'm making a master list of interface dramas here for people to play and hopefully build support for this unique type of game. 
        </description>
        <link>https://chostett.com/interface-drama</link>
        <pubDate>
            Thu, 17 Aug 2023 13:17:32 +0000
        </pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
        <title>Interface Dramas: A New Way of Telling Stories Through Software</title>
        <description>
             Our generation grew up online. So it's only natural that stories told by our generation are, by their nature, defined by the online spaces they inhabit. In this talk, CJ and mabbees talk about a new genre of games; interface dramas, and why they redefine the way our generation and younger will tell stories.
        </description>
        <link>https://chostett.com/talks/202212-interface-drama</link>
        <pubDate>
            Tue, 15 Aug 2023 05:46:52 +0000
        </pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
        <title>unexpectedly hopeful</title>
        <description>
             In my last update, I spoke about how frustrating it was to do constant trial and error when it came to my health. After two months, I have an unexpectedly hopeful update.
        </description>
        <link>https://chostett.com/blog/posts/2023-08-02-unexpectedly-hopeful</link>
        <pubDate>
            Wed, 02 Aug 2023 18:00:00 +0000
        </pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
        <title>Finding a Home on the Internet</title>
        <description>
             I was eleven when I made my first Angelfire site. The site has the feel of a kid's room; nothing matches and the only theme binding them together is, "CJ likes this."
        </description>
        <link>https://chostett.com/blog/posts/2023-07-01-Finding-a-Home-on-the-Internet</link>
        <pubDate>
            Sat, 15 Jul 2023 10:00:00 +0000
        </pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
        <title>How Technology Spreads Bias: And How You Can Stop It</title>
        <description>
             An interactive workshop centered around small-group discussions tailored to digging in deep about racism, homophobia, transphobia, and other kinds of biases prevalent in tech.
        </description>
        <link>https://chostett.com/talks/202306-bias-in-tech</link>
        <pubDate>
            Fri, 30 Jun 2023 10:00:00 +0000
        </pubDate>
    </item>

</channel>
</rss>